## Jamie Otelsberg

Graphic Design, Design Research

ammasvilasini@gmail.com

## Summary

I've been working as a Team Lead in Graphics for the past 6 years at AMMACHI Labs, which was a wonderful exposure to many types of projects and lead to the development of the following skill sets: - Graphic Design - Web Design - UX Research - UI Design - Storyboarding - Information Architecture - 3D Production Management - 2D Animation - Illustration -Design for Professional Presentations - Team Management I take a serious interest in User Experience design for software applications that serve rural and low-literate populations and have participated in a number of usability tests conducted by AMMACHI Labs.

## Experience

#### Graphic Designer at AMMACHI Labs

2009 - Present (6 years)

Graphic Design, UI Design, UX Research and HCI

#### Graphics Team Lead at AMMACHI Labs

2009 - Present (6 years)

Management of 2D and 3D artists for a variety of projects, including animation for eLearning content, 3D objects for use in Haptic software applications, UI design, illustration, and graphic design for marketing materials and web.

## Education

#### **Udacity**

Front End Web Development, 2014 - 2015

#### **Sessions College**

Certification - 2D Animation, Animation

## Skills & Expertise

**Graphic Design** 

**Art Direction** 

**Team Management** 

**UI Design** 

#### **Publications**

Issues in the User Interface Design of a Content Rich Vocational Training Application for Digitally Illiterate Users

World Academy of Science, Engineering and Technology 2013

Authors: Jamie Otelsberg, Nagarajan Akshay, Rao R. Bhavani

This paper discusses our preliminary experiences in the design of a user interface of a computerized contentrich vocational training courseware meant for users with little or no computer experience.

## **Projects**

### MySangham UI Design, Information Architecture

Members:Jamie Otelsberg

Research, Information Architecture, Web Design, UI Design for mysangham.com.

# **Jamie Otelsberg**

Graphic Design, Design Research

ammasvilasini@gmail.com



Contact Jamie on LinkedIn